myfolio.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy | MyFolio

MyFolio.com's Privacy Policy hereby states the policies regarding MyFolio.com's treatment of any personal information that MyFolio.com may receive and collect from users via the use of the MyFolio.com website or during the registration process and website usage.

## MyFolio.com Registration and Personal Information

MyFolio.com collects personal information from users during the MyFolio.com registration process, with the use of the MyFolio.com website, or when you visit the pages of certain MyFolio.com partners' websites. During the registration process at the MyFolio.com website, we will ask for information such as your name, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, e-mail address and personal interests. MyFolio.com automatically receives browser information such as your IP address, MyFolio.com cookie information, and the page(s) you visit.

Users may include personal information such as name, location, occupation, skill set, and e-mail address on their Portfolio. Users understand that by including personal information in their Portfolio, they are making it readily available to the general public and are doing so at their own risk and discretion. MyFolio.com assumes no liability or responsibility for the mistreatment or wrongful use of personal information by other users and/or visitors.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

MyFolio.com will never rent, sell, or share personal information about its users with non-affiliated companies or individuals, except to provide a product or service that has been requested by such a user or if MyFolio.com has that user's permission. MyFolio.com may display targeted advertisements that are based on a user's personal information. In such scenarios, Advertisers understand that the user who interacts with, views, or clicks such targeted ads meets the demographic requirements (i.e., men ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area) for their product's target audience. MyFolio.com will not provide personal information to the advertiser upon interaction or viewing of a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing such an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. If you click on an advertisement at MyFolio.com, you are not required nor obligated to purchase a good or service. MyFolio.com is not liable for any purchases made through an advertisement on the MyFolio.com website.

In the event of a subpoena, court order or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, information may be shared in order to protect the interests of MyFolio.com. At MyFolio.com, we believe it is necessary to share information when it is required by law, as it will help expedite an investigation, prevent or help take action against illegal activities, suspend on suspicion of fraud, or help protect against a potential threat to the physical safety of an individual or violation of MyFolio.com's Terms of Use.

In the event of a company merger or acquisition, MyFolio.com may transfer information about you. In such a scenario, MyFolio.com will notify its members before the information is transferred as personal information may become subject to another privacy policy.

## MyFolio.com Cookies

MyFolio.com may set and access cookies on your computer once you use the MyFolio.com website. MyFolio.com allows Advertisers that advertise on the MyFolio.com website to set and access cookies on your computer as well. Advertisers may use the cookies they set at their own discretion, as regulated by their privacy policies. Advertisers or other 3rd party companies do not, nor will they ever, have access to MyFolio.com's cookie information.

## Links

MyFolio.com may contain links to different websites. MyFolio.com is not responsible for, nor is its information governed by, the privacy policies and/or practices on the linked websites. When linking to another website, users are urged to read and understand the privacy policy posted on that website. Our privacy policy only governs the information collected on and the use of the MyFolio.com website.

## Confidentiality and Security

In compliance with Federal regulations, in order to help maintain the privacy of personal information, the access of personal information by MyFolio.com employees is limited to those who are in reasonable need of such information to perform their job functions; whether it is to come into contact with a member to provide a company notice, to provide products or services, or for customer service or technical issues.

## Note

MyFolio.com may update its Privacy Policy periodically. MyFolio may update the Privacy Policy at any time, and without actual notice to you. All such changes to Privacy Policy will appear on this page ([myfolio.com/privacy](http://myfolio.com/privacy)). By using this site, you agree to all present and future changes. If at any time you choose not to accept our Privacy Policy, you may delete your account and discontinue using the website.

## Contacting MyFolio.com

If you have any questions about our security measures, the privacy practices of this site or just have any general questions or suggestions, please feel free to e-mail us at [help@myfolio.com,](mailto:help@myfolio.com) or use our contact form.
